https://www.globalhealthtrax.com/privacy-policy

×
Continue Shopping
Edit Cart
Returning Customer Checkout
Existing customers select this choice. Requires your login (email or customer ID) and password. If you forgot your login/password, call Customer Service at 800-305-5710.
New Customer Checkout
For retail only purchases. Requires account setup.
* Once you sign in or create your account, you’ll be able to edit the items in your cart and confirm your purchase prior to payment.
For your convenience you can add products from our sister company Vibrant Nutraceuticals to this order and have them shipped together. Click here to add products. For further information about Global Health Trax products please visit: www.vibrantnutra.com.
×
Item has been added to your cart.
Go to your cart »
MENU
Home
Free Home Test
Products
Active Digestive Enzymes
FiveLac Probiotic
Oxygen Elements® Max
SevenLac Probiotic | Lemon
SevenLac Probiotic | Apple
ThreeLac Maintenance
ThreeLac Probiotic (packets)
ThreeLac Probiotic Caps
Vegan Life Nutrition Products
Vibrant Nutraceuticals Products
About
FAQs
Management
News
Home
ThreeLac Maintenance
ThreeLac Probiotic (packets)
ThreeLac Probiotic Caps
Vegan Life Nutrition Products
Vibrant Nutraceuticals Products
About
FAQs
Management
News
Contact
Privacy Policy
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.ghthealth.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be sharedWhat choices are available to you regarding the use of your dataThe security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your informationHow you can correct any inaccuracies in the information
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Testimonials
About three years ago I went back to my lung specialist and he said, ‘I don’t know what you are doing, but whatever it is, keep it up, because it is working!’
— Rosa S.
July 5, 2019
Read More Testimonials
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if anyChange/correct any data we have about youHave us delete any data we have about youExpress any concern you have about our use of your data
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 760-542-3000 or via email at ght@globalhealthtrax.com
Articles
Featured
Joining together to fight COVID-19
Immune System Boosters
Protecting your immune system while social distancing
Marine PhytoPlankton and your immune system
Probiotics and your immune system
Vitamins
Vitamin K and COVID-19; What You Need to Know
Vitamin D2 vs. Vitamin D3. What’s the difference?
Testimonials
I have used your ThreeLac product and, I like it very much. The customer service dept. is excellent. This time I tried the ThreeLac Caps and I do like them, even though they are not lemon flavored. Thanks!!!
— B.B.
Vitamin D2 vs. Vitamin D3. What’s the difference?
Digest this! Want to be first to know about our promos, sales and other goodies?
The GHT Companies will not sell your contact information to any other entity.
×
